Seen, golly golly channel, go go go!
Today's project is a very exciting one for both of us!
Moppan 31!
No, um, 31, it's really good.
I'm excited.
It smells so good. I love ice cream.
How do you like it?
I can eat it all in one sitting.
I don't usually talk this much on YouTube, but I am talking.
Well, let's eat it now!
It's melting.
What?
Well, Yuzu recommended... what was it again?
Strawberry cheesecake.
Strawberry cheesecake, please.
Well, I'll take the high road and start with the popping shower.
Bon appétit!
Bon appétit.
It's got cake in it.
Strawberry cheesecake.
I thought it was just a flavor.
There's a big piece of cheesecake cake in there, too.
It's delicious!
Momo-san doesn't do a lot of eating projects.
It's been a while.
What should I say?
Well, Kira and the others opened the can.
They were like, "Uh-oh!
Have you ever eaten this? Cookies and cream.
No, Momo.
I'll have the ones you just had.
It's so good!
Oh, my God!
I didn't know cheesecake was this good.
How are you?
How are you?How are you?
I've been seeing him more and more every day.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Hey.
Yesterday.
I was like, "It's drawing time.
Drawing?
Yeah, I'm into drawing games.
You can do it with your friends online.
One of us draws a letter of a theme, and the others try to guess it.
One person draws a letter of the theme, and the other person guesses it.
Yesterday, after work...
I went home and told Misaki that we could do it now.
We went home and played the drawing game.
I don't know.
We ended up playing drawing games.
I don't know what it was, but it was like green tea caramel.
Hey, how's it going?
How's it going?
Oh! It's so matcha.
Caramel?
It's so matcha.
Matcha.
You're not a matcha girl, are you?
I went with regular matcha.
Dough mints have a nice color.
It's amazing.
It's so bright.
Doesn't it look great?
They call it toothpaste.
What kind of toothpaste do you use?
What?
Sistema.
Is that what you're saying?
It's a combination of Systema and Mondamine.
Oh my God, it's so good!Oh man, it's so delicious!
I've loved chocolate mint since I was a wee one.
Love Potion 31
This is so good!
I had a friend in high school.
I had a friend in high school who really liked 31.
We were the best of friends.
She was a huge influence on me.
I ate a lot of it last year.
I ate a lot of toato.
I ate it in between the three leaves.
Whenever I hung out with my friends, I ate 31.
I ate so much when I was in elementary school.
Regular?
I ate the biggest size of ice cream, triple, so much.
I really love it that much.
I ate 31 on YouTube for the second time.
31?
I used to eat them like toato's off day.
But they don't come around very often, do they?
Unless you have a friend who really likes it.
Unless you have a friend you really like.
Isn't that great?
Candy, cookies...
There was one that had marshmallows in it for a while.
Who in the world makes that kind of ice cream?
But Yuzu, you definitely want to work at 31 at least once.
That's pretty much what I've been saying.
31 misses.
But... this is how you get the ice cream.
I hear it's really hard on the arms.
That's true.
They're not in a soft state.
Is there anything you'd like to do together?
What? I don't know.
Something you'd like to do with the whole group?What do you want to do with all the members?
On the contrary, what?
Sleepover with everyone.
And play arcade games together.
And play Spo-cha.
Spo-cha.
And I want to go to Tondemi Heiwajima again.
I want to spend the whole day there.
You know what I mean?
I know. I know.
I really want to go there.
I also want to go to Jumperland.
Where?
Yuzu's at Disney.
Sounds fun.
You like Disney, don't you?
I've never been to Doujinshi.
We went together, right?
We did.
That treacherous Disney trip.
I worked for Yuzu.
Momochan.
My mom is a Momo-chan fan.
She always says
When I talk about Momochan...
Momochan is a slow eater.
She's cute in that way, too.
She's really slow.
You're really slow.
Yuzu eats fast.
No, I'm not.
But we're...
I've already told you.
My mother is slower than Momo.
So it's probably genetic.
I'm the last one to eat school lunch.He was alone at lunch until the end.
What's that?
When I was in kindergarten...
After lunch, it was time to clean up.
I ate alone while cleaning.
You don't like to eat while cleaning?
No.
But my mom made a face for me.
She made a face for me.
I couldn't eat it. I felt like it was a waste.
I was like, "What should I do?
I've already started cleaning.
Please eat it.
It wasn't a character bento at first.
Momochan told me she thought my bento didn't look good.
She came home crying.
Since then, she's been making kyaraben every day without fail.
Isn't that nice?
Isn't that sweet?
What was the worst thing that happened to you when you were little?
I don't know.
Yes, I do.
I have a cell phone for kids.
You know, the kind of cell phone that watches over you?
You wash it in the washing machine.
I washed something.
I got really pissed off.
He gets really mad at me for that.
He's really mad at me.
They get really mad at me for that.
I'm serious.
So ever since then, I try not to put too much in my pockets.
I'm growing up.Growing up.
I'm going to go with the kids' cell phone connection.
I used to be like three years old when I got my first cell phone.
It was a Gala phone.
Three years old with a cell phone.
It's like a kids' cell phone.
And when you poke the tip of the phone, a round thing comes out and you pull it.
And when you pull it, it's like this.
It's like a security buzzer.
Same thing.
It's like a buzzer that contacts your family.
Yeah...
I don't know what it was, but it stuck.
I kept saying it over and over.
Well...
I've been doing it like this.
I'm getting calls from my mom and dad.
They'll call my dad, who's at work.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I can't even text properly.
Yeah. - Yeah.
It's like they don't know who they're sending it to.
That's true, that's true.
That's why I've caused so much trouble so many times.
Just like Momochan.
You know, sometimes I get emails I thought I was sending to my grandma, but they come to me.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
Does it come back?
Yeah, she's coming back.
You ate a lot.
I ate a lot.
Momo's just late.
Yeah, right.
We'll eat the rest together.
Such a happy project.Such a happy project.
Thank you very much.
I know you were probably wondering what I was talking about halfway through.
Thank you very much for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel and leave a comment!
Thank you very much!
Bye-bye!
Your tongue's not in your head.
Who is it?
Lana and I.
I'm wearing a costume by Deeholic this time.
Thank you for watching.